Guide to the Jerry Clapsaddle papers, 1981-2005
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Jerry Clapsaddle papers
1981-2005
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Jerry Clapsaddle, 1941-
C0064
10 linear feet (24 boxes)
This collection contains materials pertaining to Jerry Clapsaddle's career as a professor of art at George Mason University. Materials include annual reports, correspondence, slides, and videotapes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Jerry Clapsaddle in 2005-2006.
Biographical Information
Jerry Clapsaddle was an art professor at George Mason University from 1982-2005. During his career at George Mason University, Clapsaddle worked to promote the public exhibition of student and faculty art. In 1987 he founded ArtsBus, a program of the Department of Art and Visual Technology (later the School of Art) in the College of Visual and Performing Arts at George Mason University, which plans field trips for art students to galleries in New York, Philadelphia, and Richmond.
Scope and Content
Contains materials pertaining to Clapsaddle's career at George Mason University, including memoranda and correspondence between Clapsaddle and University administrators, student feedback on the ArtsBus program, and information on the NEA-funded Arts in Public Places (AIPP) program in northern Virginia and Washington, D.C. Series 1 contains the subject files of the collection. In this series, there are correspondences, biographical material, and administrative information for the George Mason University school of art, the ArtsBus and Art in Public Places. The administrative information contains financial statements, annual reports and reviews and other material on the day to day business. Series 2 contains photographs, slides and audio cassette tapes. This section presents artwork from George Mason University students as well as others. Series 3 contains VHS tapes of student art projects, along with a video guide and a faculty handbook.
Arrangement
Organized into three series.
Series 1: Subject Files, 1981-2004 (Boxes 1-7)
Series 2: Photographs and Slides, 1973-2002 (Box 8)
Series 3: Videotapes, 1995-2000 (Boxes 9-10)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Special Collections and Archives also holds the George Mason University Archives.
Index Terms
Persons:
Clapsaddle, Jerry, 1941-
Corporate Names:
George Mason University. School of Art.
Subjects:
Art in universities and colleges--Virginia, Northern.
Document Types:
Photographic prints.; Slides.; Video recordings
Contents List
- Series 1: Subject Files, 1981-2004; (7 boxes)
  This series contains office material from Jerry Clapsaddle's time as a professor of art, including correspondence, annual reports, files on the ArtsBus and museums, and information on the Art in Public Places program.
  - George Mason University Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Getting Hired
  - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Goals
  - Renewal, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Faculty Profile
  - Space, Buildings and Grounds, November, 1981 - November, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Floor Plans
  - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Memorandums, Annual Report, Arts Gala
  - 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Memorandums, Travel Request, Postcard
  - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, Papermaking Workshop, Accounting Report,
  - Annual Report, August, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Curriculum Vita - Tenure Application, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - PT Letters from Carol Mattusch and Committee, November, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Promotion and Tenure Committee
  - Promotion and Tenure Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Correspondence
  - Curriculum Vitae Preparation, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Biographical and Professional Material from 1941-1986
  - Annual Report, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report - Cover Letter and Information, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Workshop and Visiting Artists Proposals, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report II, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report III, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Annual Report IV, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - George Mason University Salary, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Facts and Figures Comparisons
  - 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, Postcard, Petree Graphics
  - Annual Report, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report II, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Annual Review, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Carol - Issues, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - George Mason University Salary Issue, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Report II, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Annual Review, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Study Leave Research Records, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - George Mason University Appointments and Renewals, 1981-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, Department Responsibilities
  - Studio Issues, September, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - George Mason University Loan Forms, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alex Jamison VIT, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, Fellowships, Tenure Track Faculty
  - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report 1990 Descriptive Information, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, Report, Pamphlets
  - Annual Review, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, Articles, "On Teaching at a Second-Rate University" by Terry Caesar
  - Annual Report, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Student Art Insurance and Security, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, Newspaper Article
  - Ron Lauzon (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Bachelor of Individual Study
  - Glen Belfiore (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Bachelors of Individual Study
  - Field Trip Reports from Professor Goldman, September, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    New York, Student Reports
  - ArtsBus Feedback, November, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ArtsBus Feedback - Goldman, November, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - ArtsBus Feedback - Uptown, November, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - ArtsBus Feedback, October, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - ArtsBus Feedback - Lauren, October, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - ArtsBus Feedback - Goldman, October, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - ArtsBus Feedback - Constantine, October, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ArtsBus Feedback - Sandberg, September, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ArtsBus Comments, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ArtsBus Inquiries, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Art, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Name Listings, Articles
  - ArtsBus New York, September, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - ArtsBus, October, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - ArtsBus, November, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - ArtsBus, September, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Bryan Smith, New York, The Week Art, Luhring Augustine "On the Tightrope"
  - ArtsBus, March, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Cancelled
  - ArtsBus, February, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    CUE Art, New York
  - ArtsBus, November, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    CUE Art, Participant List
  - ArtsBus, October, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    New York, The Art World, Participant List
  - ArtsBus, September, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    New York, Correspondence
  - ArtsBus Website and Brochure, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Development
  - ArtsBus Overnights, May, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Overnight to New York, Honors Seminar
  - ArtsBus, April, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    New York
  - ArtsBus, February, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    New York, Correspondence, Carolee Schneemann
  - ArtsBus, April 21, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Receipts, Correspondence, Participant List, Wait List, New York
  - ArtsBus, March 24, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    Art and Visual Technologies, Correspondence, Participant List, Itinerary, New York
  - ArtsBus, February 24, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    Receipts, Contracts, Correspondence, New York
  - ArtsBus, November 18, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    New York, Wait List, Participant List,
  - ArtsBus, October 21, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    Participant List, New York
  - ArtsBus, September 23, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Davor Vrankic, Participant List, Letter of Complaint, New York
  - ArtsBus, April 22, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    New York, Participant List, Wait List
  - ArtsBus Philadelphia, March-April, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Flier
  - Philadelphia ArtsBus, March-April, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Invoices, Fliers, Correspondence, Brochures
  - ArtsBus, March 25, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    New York, Participant List, Guides
  - ArtsBus, February 26, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Correspondence, Participant List, Art Magazine, Wait List, New York
  - ArtsBus, November 20, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, Arts Bus Video Advertisement, Mark Stevens, Participant List
  - ArtsBus Richmond, October 30, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, Risk Release Agreement,
  - ArtsBus, October, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, Wait List
  - ArtsBus, September, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Participant List, Response to Student Comments, Receipts
  - ArtsBus, February 27, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    New York, Articles
  - ArtsBus, April 24, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    New York, Art Mark Stevens, War Stories, The Museum of Modern Art
  - ArtsBus, March 27, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Flier, Chuck Close, Robert Storr
  - ArtsBus, March 21, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    New York, Participant List
  - ArtsBus, September 26, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    New York, Flier, Correspondence, Art Magazine Copy
  - ArtsBus, October 24, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    New York, Flier, Correspondence
  - ArtsBus, November 21, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    New York, Chris Martin
  - ArtsBus, April 18, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    New York,
  - ArtsBus, September 27, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - ArtsBus, November 21, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    New York, Art Magazine Copy, Correspondence
  - ArtsBus, February 21, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - ArtsBus, November 22, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    New York, Correspondence, Museum of Modern Art
  - ArtsBus, October 25, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - ArtsBus, April 19, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - ArtsBus, March 22, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ArtsBus, November 2, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    New York, Fliers, Brochures, Pratt Institute, Articles
  - ArtsBus, October 5, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    New York, Meret Oppenheim "Beyond the Teacup"
  - ArtsBus Comments, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - ArtsBus Comments, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - ArtsBus Polls (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Art and Visual Technology Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Mission Statement, Correspondence, Memorandums
  - Artery, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Correspondence, Newspaper Articles, Call for Entries
  - Art and Visual Technology Promotional, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Fliers, Pamphlets, Correspondence
  - Kristin Johnsen-Neshati - Peer Review, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Course Syllabi, Articles, Correspondence
  - Art and Visual Technology, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Faculty Meetings, Memorandums
  - College of Visual and Performing Arts, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Agenda, Meetings, Training Scenarios, ByLaws
  - FATE Presentation, March, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, Forms
  - Art Issues - Education, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Annual Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Art and Visual Technology, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Meeting Minutes
  - Teaching Effectiveness Proposal, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Syllabi, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Art and Visual Technology Meeting, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Memorandums, By Laws
  - Rollins - Pyramid Atlantic, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, Article
  - Art and Visual Technology Programming, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Sculpture Proposal, Newspaper Articles, Correspondence
  - Syllabi, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Tour of Art and Visual Technologies, October 17, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Certificate of Appreciation (Box 8, Folder 9)
    20 Years of Service
  - 2004 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Memorandums, Correspondence, Convocation
  - Reference Letters, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Non-Student Letters of Reference, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Student Recommendations, 1987-1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Graduation Awards, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Patricia Keller, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Personal Mythology
  - Alumni To Contact, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Letter to Alumni and Community, February 4, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Alumni, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Alumni Lists Class of 1976 and Forward
  - Print Alumni, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - IOA Newsletter, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Fliers, Newsletters, Pamphlets
  - Former Students Correspondence, 1983-1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, Cards
  - Alumni to Contact, 1983-1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Art Studio News, August-October, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence Former Students, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Current Students, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Students and Alumni Achievement Forms, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Alumni News, 1992-1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Articles, Correspondence
  - Print Alumni, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Alumni to Contact, 2000-2002 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Convocation, Correspondence
  - Finance, 1987-1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, Financial Records
  - Art in Public Places, 1983-1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, Forms, Progress Reports
  - Public Art, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Pamphlets, Post Cards, Examples of Public Art
  - Investment Advice, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Pamphlets
  - Art in Public Places Commemorative, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Newspaper Articles
  - Art in Public Places Competitions, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Newspaper Article, Pamphlets
  - Art in Pubic Places Elsewhere, 1984-1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Articles, Pamphlets, Booklets
  - Art in Public Places - Siah Armajani, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Correspondence, Contract
  - Art in Public Places - Siah Armajani II, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Correspondence, Cultural Park Map and Plans
  - Art in Public Places Expenses, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Budget Reports
  - Receipts, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Art in Public Places Planning Grant, 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Art in Public Places Book Information, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Art in Public Places Policy, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Art in Public Places - Jackie Ferrara, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Art in Public Places Planning Committee, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Art in Public Places Campus Projects, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    University of Massachusetts Art Council
  - Art in Public Places - Philadelphia (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Pamphlets, Guide to Philadelphia Architecture
  - Art in Public Places - Rockville, Maryland, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Art in Public Places University Campuses, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Vietnam Memorial, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Art in Public Places Artists, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Art in Public Places File, 1980-1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Magazines, Newspaper Articles
  - Art in Public Places Contracts, 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Art in Public Places Artists - DePalma, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Ballston Gateway Proposal
  - Art in Public Places Artists - Holt, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Urban Design
  - National Airport, July, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Newspapers
  - Art in Public Places Consultants - Yahalem, June, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Art in Public Places Organizations and Projects, 1984-1989 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Booklets, Newsletters
  - Rockville Art in Public Places, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Art in Public Places - Partners for Livable Places, 1989-1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Art in Public Places Olympics, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Art in Public Places - Battery Park, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Art in Public Places - Proposals, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Committee for Public Art, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Art in Public Places - Philadelphia Conference, October, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Art in Public Places Conference - Smithsonian, April, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Building the Modern City
  - Art in Public Places - Urban Planning (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Newsletter
  - Art in Public Places, James Center Proposal, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Art in Public Places, James Center Studies, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Art in Public Places - King Street Station Park, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Art in Public Places - PADC, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Art in Public Places Publications (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Livability, Art in Form
  - Art in Public Places, 1988-1992 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - AIDS Quilt, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Partners for Livable Spaces - Amenities, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Roger Tomhave, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, Articles
  - 1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, Events, Awards
  - Annual Report, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Goals, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Artifact Meeting, August, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, Plan for the Arts
  - Annual Report, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Department Future - Position Papers, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Possible Split Between Art and Art History
  - Department Future - Polls, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Art and Education Defense Issues, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Department Future - College of Arts and Sciences, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Departmental Future - Sheila Ellen, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Educational Reform, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Statements, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Art Statements, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Departmental Future - University Notes, December, 1992-January, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Studio Future, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, Prospectus
  - Institute of Arts Student Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Annual Review, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, Text Suggestions, Calendar
  - Exhibition Assessments, 1993-1995 (Box 14)
  - Outside Funding for the Arts, 1995-1997 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - CD Rom Grant, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Arts Agenda, Spring, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Student Work Loan Records, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Artreach Exhibition, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - 1995 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Goals, Teaching, Articles, Fliers, Studio Fundamentals,
  - Annual Report and Reviews, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Institute of Arts Retreat, May, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, Short on Faculty
  - Arts Budget, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Student Funding, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Arts, Spring, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Faculty Agenda
  - Course, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Course Lists, Fliers, Correspondence
  - Arts Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition Schedules, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Goals, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - South East College Arts Conference, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Evans, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    Correspondence, Meeting
  - Student Achievements, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Studio Description, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - George Mason University Teaching Awards, 1995-1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Instructional Rating Reports, Events, Booklets
  - 1998 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    Faculty Workload, Art Studies Handbook
  - Arts, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    Mission Statement, Meeting Minutes
  - Web Page, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    New Website
  - Facility Needs, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Arts Budget, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Scheduling and Staff, 1996-1999 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Restructuring, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Correspondence, Drafts for Restructuring Ideas
  - Annual Report, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Exhibitions, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Newsletter, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    First Issue of Platform
  - Suzanne Carbonneau Tenure Dossier, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Arts and Visual Technologies Curriculum Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Discussion of Curriculum Changes
  - Bachelor of Arts and Bachelor of Fine Arts Revisions, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Record of Issues, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Correspondence, Institute of Arts Peer Review
  - ArtBus Videos, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    VHS Price Lists, Video Catalogs
  - ArtBus - New York City, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - ArtsBus Overnight Feedback, April, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - ArtsBus Feedback, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - ArtsBus Pay Paper Trail, 1995-1998 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Expenses, Copy
  - ArtsBus History, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - ArtsBus Funding, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - ArtsBus New York City Trip and Death Watch, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - ArtsBus Comments, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - ArtsBus Daytrip Feedback, April, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - ArtsBus Marketing, 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Correspondence, Newspaper Articles, Booklets, Fliers
  - ArtsBus, March 23, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Itinerary, New York City
  - ArtsBus, Fall, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    Correspondence, Articles on Events
  - ArtsBus, October 20, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    Correspondence, Expenses, Exhibition Information, New York City
  - ArtsBus Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - ArtsBus New York City, Magazine and Newspaper Articles (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - ArtsBus Information, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Correspondence, Newspaper Articles, Notes
  - ArtsBus Information, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Art Guides
  - Rauschenberg (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Epic Vision, Review
  - ArtsBus, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    New York City, Arts Guide
  - ArtsBus Problems, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Subway, Buses, Tour Masters, Risk Forms, New York City Artists and Art Dealers, New York City Maps
  - ArtsBus Future, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - ArtsBus - Places to Eat, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Newspaper Articles, Restaurant Reviews
  - ArtsBus Metropolitan Museum, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, Guide Books
  - ArtsBus - Articles on Current Exhibitions, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - New York City ArtsBus, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - ArtsBus, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Articles, Museum References
  - ArtsBus Expenses, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - ArtsBus Expenses Before 1999, 1983-1998 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - ArtsBus Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - ArtsBus Financial, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - ArtsBus Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Memorandums, Financial Statements
  - ArtsBus Future, 2002-2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Correspondence, Newspaper Articles
  - Trish Mandes Article, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - ArtsBus Overnights, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - ArtsBus Meeting, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    Notes
  - ArtsBus, April, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    Board List, New York City, Overnight Trip
  - ArtBus - New World Trade Center, November, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - ArtsBus - Egon Verheyen, November, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - David Tannous, 1990-1998 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - ArtsBus - Articles on Current Exhibitions, 2001-2002 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - ArtsBus - Listings of Current Performances, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - ArtsBus - Listings of Current Performances, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Extras, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    Maps and Exhibition Lists for New York City
  - Kirby Malone, 1998-2003 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Series 2: Photographs and Slides, 1973-2002; (1 box)